<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<!-- The Living Fire -->
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_1_0">
		<text>Snitch told me to meet you. You know something that could shed some light on the "fiery" stalker from the rumors, right?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_1_1">
		<text>Ah, yes... I've got something, but don't get your hopes too high. Some time ago we've observed weird flashes happening at night behind the huge garbage pile south of us, followed by some terrifying howling of mutants. Some loners were curious what's happened there and visited the place during the day. They've found some dead fleshes there which were... well.. slightly grilled. At first we thought that those fleshes got into some hardly visible anomaly that disappeared the next day or encountered a flame poltergeist, but there was one peculiar thing about one of them. It had something that looked like a brand on its back - it was in the shape of a human hand. It could have been a simple accident... or not? Who knows...\n \nYou could have a look around here at night if you'd like to find out more. If that guy really exists, then his affinity with fire might be a good clue where you should look for him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_1_2">
		<text>Hmm... this still sounds like some veteran story to scare rookies. Either way, I'll try to find out something more. Thanks.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_1_3">
		<text>Yeah... I've got to admit it sounds nuts. You should still watch your back. The Zone is a strange place...\nAnyway - Snitch owes me one round for this, no matter what's the outcome of your investigation.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_2_0">
		<text>I'm back from my sear...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_2_1">
		<text>Let me guess. You've just wasted time chasing yet another rumor for Snitch, am I ri...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_2_2">
		<text>I saw him... that stalker from the rumor.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_2_3">
		<text>You saw... what? Are you serious now? Wait... you look a little pale... You're serious?! Does it have something to do with that loud explision that we heard?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_2_4">
		<text>Yes. He was doing some sort of... ritual... at the Greek Fire anomaly. There was fire everywhere around. A stray flesh came close and got... evaporated?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_2_5">
		<text>How the hell are you alive then, huh? Did you talk with him?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_2_6">
		<text>I don't know. He has certainly been aware of my presence from the beginning, even though he didn't see me. When I wanted to ask who he is, he interrupted me saying that everyone will know his name and disappeared in a fiery explosion shortly after.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_2_7">
		<text>Everyone will know his name, huh? That doesn't sound good. Well - at least Snitch will be happy to hear that you've found something. Now he definitely owes me a whole bottle.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_2_0">
		<text>Snitch - we need to talk.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_2_1">
		<text>The rumor turned out to be true. I know... I've already received a message from my friend. You've done well. Here - you've earned it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_2_2">
		<text>Five thousands? Are you out of your mind? I could have died there!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_2_3">
		<text>Shhh... shut it. There's more to come. Work for me a bit more and you'll get it. We need to find out more. People won't pay much just for the information that this stalker exists. Well... maybe Petrenko will, given that he's lost two men because of him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_2_4">
		<text>So what's the plan now? We don't know where he went or what's his goal. We have no leads.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_2_5">
		<text>We do. When you've been doing your investigation, I've overheard a talk between two scientists about some abnormal anomalous activity exactly at the place where you've met the stranger. You should go and talk with Sakharov and offer your help investigating the issue.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_2_6">
		<text>Fine. I'll be on my way then.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_2_7">
		<text>Just one more thing. Don't mention to him that it was me who was eavesdropping on his colleagues. I don't want them to be more cautious around me. Scientific information tends to be pretty valuable.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_0">
		<text>Professor - may I have a word with you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_1">
		<text>Not now young man. We're busy investigating some recent incident.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_2">
		<text>Is that matter by any chance related to the Greek Fire anomaly?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_3">
		<text>How did you know? Did you intercept some message that I sent to my assistants?! This information is classified!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_4">
		<text>Don't get upset, professor. It's irrelevant how I did find out. The thing is - I've been there not long time ago when something weird happened and I'm willing to share my knowledge with you if you agree to disclose what you know. This would be mutually beneficial. Maybe I could assist you with...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_5">
		<text>Didn't I make myself clear?! This information is class... wait... You say you've seen something there? What was it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_6">
		<text>Knowledge for knowledge professor. I can assure you that my information is worth it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_7">
		<text>Damn you... so be it. Our scanners have been showing some abnormal readings from that anomaly for a few days now - sudden spikes in the energy it emitted. Just as if the anomaly was expanding and going back to its base state. We've seen fluctuations like this in other anomalies before, although not with this frequency. We've decided to ignore it. Not long time ago our readings went off scale at night for a short time before going back to normal. This is very worrying. We might be in big trouble if anomalies start to expand uncontrollably.\n \nNow please tell me, what have you seen there? I assume you've seen many anomalies in your life, so it had to be something extraordinary.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_8">
		<text>Yes - it was. Just like you said, the anomaly was really active at that time. It was spewing a lot of flames. What's the most interesting is that there was a man among those flames. He was performing some kind of ritual. What I found out later is that he can somehow control the fire. He literally disintegrated a flesh on my eyes. After a short time, he bursted into flames and disappeard. That's also when the flames went dormant again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_9">
		<text>That's fascinating! So it was him who empowered the anomaly. Did you have a chance to talk with him?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_10">
		<text>No - unfortunately not... though he said that in time everyone will know his name.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_11">
		<text>This doesn't sound well given what power he has. We need to find out what he wants to achieve.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_12">
		<text>I agree and I've got to say I hoped that you could tell me where I should head next.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_13">
		<text>I'm afraid I can't help you with that. Our scanners didn't show anything else for... wait... there it is! The scanners are showing unnatural activity at the Fault anomaly. You should head there immediately!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_14">
		<text>Thank you, professor! I'll be going then.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
