<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_new_tasks_addon_dead_night_name">
		<text>Dead Night</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_new_tasks_addon_dead_night_text">
		<text>Loners are disappearing without a trace during the night in the Darkscape. Sidorovich asked me to find out what's going on.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_new_tasks_addon_dead_night_about">
		<text>Our lads have reported that some Loners have disappeared recently on their way from the Darkscape sawmill to our village. The path was always relatively safe, so folks often traveled at night to avoid bandits and soliders. Their screams in the dark were heard by the guys staying at the sawmill, but noone was brave enough to risk their life trying to help them. The bodies of the missing stalkers have not been found after the dawn. Stalkers around here have gathered a small sum for someone willing to investigate what happened.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_new_tasks_addon_dead_night_finish">
		<text>What a horrible fate... thank you for putting the dead to their final rest and making sure no more lads will join their forces. Here - you've earned it.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="dead_night_details">
        <text>Investigate the place during the night</text>
    </string>

	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_skyfall_name">
		<text>Skyfall</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_skyfall_text">
		<text>The military has received reinforcements in form of new Mi-24 helicopter that might be used for assaulting the old military warehouses where Freedom resides. Lukash has tasked me with taking down this flying beast. I should get to Agroprom as soon as possible.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_skyfall_about">
		<text>You know - the Duty is not our only problem around here. The army would also like to take back our base to set control over the center of the Zone. What's holding them back is resources stretched thin... or at least that was the case till recently. One of our squads was blasted to pieces by a Mi-24 helicopter. Only one man has lived to tell the story. We need to act before they gather more forces. \n \nNow - I won't say it's an easy mission... there's a big chance you'll not come out of it in one piece, but if you succeed, a good money will be waiting for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_skyfall_finish">
		<text>Now that's my man! I don't think we'll need to worry about those fuckers after they saw your fireworks.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="skyfall_details">
        <text>Destroy the helicopter</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skyfall_stealth_message">
        <text>You sneaky bastard! So you've decided to take care of it silently. I couldn't have planned it better myself! Now don't screw it and try to plant some explosives somewhere where noone will see them.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skyfall_run_fail_message">
        <text>So you've ran away... I had a feeling I've chosen the wrong person for this job...</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skyfall_confrontation_message">
        <text>You think we can't see you, stalker? Coming here was your last mistake.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skyfall_cover_blow_message">
        <text>We've got a sneaky rat here!</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skyfall_blow_cover_run_message">
        <text>I see you! You're not gonna get away, stalker!</text>
    </string>

	<string id="bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_hold_the_ground_name">
		<text>Hold the Ground</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_hold_the_ground_text">
		<text>Bandits are preparing to storm the Garbage with big numbers and establish a full control over it. Petrenko asked me to bunker down at the Flea Market and push them back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_hold_the_ground_about">
		<text>Our scouts have reported a huge congregation of bandits close to the passage between the Dark Valley and Garbage. Letting them establish control over the Garbage is unacceptable. We do have problems with manpower though because of the damn hippies in the north... and that's why I'm going to send you on this mission alone. I know - it sounds like a madness, but you should receive some help from the loners that often visit that place, provided that they weren't already ambushed by some smaller detachment of bandits.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_hold_the_ground_finish">
		<text>Great job, comrade! Here - this is for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hold_the_ground_on_position_message">
        <text>The enemy has started the advance! Prepare for battle, staker!</text>
    </string>
	<string id="hold_the_ground_defended_position_message">
        <text>That should be the last of them. Report to me immediately stalker!</text>
    </string>
	<string id="hold_the_ground_run_fail_message">
        <text>Pathetic... shouldn't have trusted you on this job</text>
    </string>
	<string id="hold_the_ground_details">
        <text>Defend position</text>
    </string>
</string_table>
