<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_new_tasks_addon_dead_night_name">
		<text>Dead Night</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_new_tasks_addon_dead_night_text">
		<text>Loners are disappearing without a trace during the night in the Darkscape. Sidorovich asked me to find out what's going on.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_new_tasks_addon_dead_night_about">
		<text>Our lads have reported that some Loners have disappeared recently on their way from the Darkscape sawmill to our village. The path was always relatively safe, so folks often traveled at night to avoid bandits and soliders. Their screams in the dark were heard by the guys staying at the sawmill, but noone was brave enough to risk their life trying to help them. The bodies of the missing stalkers have not been found after the dawn. Stalkers around here have gathered a small sum for someone willing to investigate what happened.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_new_tasks_addon_dead_night_finish">
		<text>What a horrible fate... thank you for putting the dead to their final rest and making sure no more lads will join their forces. Here - you've earned it.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="dead_night_details">
        <text>Investigate the place during the night</text>
    </string>

	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_skyfall_name">
		<text>Skyfall</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_skyfall_text">
		<text>The military has received reinforcements in form of new Mi-24 helicopter that might be used for assaulting the old military warehouses where Freedom resides. Lukash has tasked me with taking down this flying beast. I should get to Agroprom as soon as possible.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_skyfall_about">
		<text>You know - the Duty is not our only problem around here. The army would also like to take back our base to set control over the center of the Zone. What's holding them back is resources stretched thin... or at least that was the case till recently. One of our squads was blasted to pieces by a Mi-24 helicopter. Only one man has lived to tell the story. We need to act before they gather more forces. \n \nNow - I won't say it's an easy mission... there's a big chance you'll not come out of it in one piece, but if you succeed, a good money will be waiting for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_skyfall_finish">
		<text>Now that's my man! I don't think we'll need to worry about those fuckers after they saw your fireworks.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="skyfall_details">
        <text>Destroy the helicopter</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skyfall_stealth_message">
        <text>You sneaky bastard! So you've decided to take care of it silently. I couldn't have planned it better myself! Now don't screw it and try to plant some explosives somewhere where noone will see them.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skyfall_run_fail_message">
        <text>So you've ran away... I had a feeling I've chosen the wrong person for this job...</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skyfall_confrontation_message">
        <text>You think we can't see you, stalker? Coming here was your last mistake.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skyfall_cover_blow_message">
        <text>We've got a sneaky rat here!</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skyfall_blow_cover_run_message">
        <text>I see you! You're not gonna get away, stalker!</text>
    </string>

	<string id="bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_hold_the_ground_name">
		<text>Hold the Ground</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_hold_the_ground_text">
		<text>Bandits are preparing to storm the Garbage with big numbers and establish a full control over it. Petrenko asked me to bunker down at the Flea Market and push them back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_hold_the_ground_about">
		<text>Our scouts have reported a huge congregation of bandits close to the passage between the Dark Valley and Garbage. Letting them establish control over the Garbage is unacceptable. We do have problems with manpower though because of the damn hippies in the north... and that's why I'm going to send you on this mission alone. I know - it sounds like a madness, but you should receive some help from the loners that often visit that place, provided that they weren't already ambushed by some smaller detachment of bandits.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_hold_the_ground_finish">
		<text>Great job, comrade! Here - this is for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hold_the_ground_on_position_message">
        <text>The enemy has started the advance! Prepare for battle, staker!</text>
    </string>
	<string id="hold_the_ground_defended_position_message">
        <text>That should be the last of them. Report to me immediately stalker!</text>
    </string>
	<string id="hold_the_ground_run_fail_message">
        <text>Pathetic... shouldn't have trusted you on this job</text>
    </string>
	<string id="hold_the_ground_details">
        <text>Defend position</text>
    </string>

	<string id="cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_no_step_back_name">
		<text>No step back</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_no_step_back_text">
		<text>Mercenaries have been steadily loosing control over Limansk and Dushman is worried that the Dead City will soon be under attack by Monolith. I've got to take back the territory up to the bridge and destroy any possible reinforcements they might receive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_no_step_back_about">
		<text>Listen up mate - I've got a personal contract for you. The status quo in Limansk has been steadily shifting in favor of Monolith recently. We might have shinier gear, but they have weapon that we've been underestimating so far - zealotry.\n\nOur lucrative business around here might end soon - some of my contractors have already left this place, because they're afraid fanatics might come here any time. Here's the deal - go to Limansk and bring back the status quo - push Monolith back behind the bridge and destory any detachments that might try to cross it again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_no_step_back_finish">
		<text>Well done. Now we can go back to the business as usuall. Here - take it. I'll make it back in no time when the new contractors find out that it's safe here again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="no_step_back_on_position_message">
        <text>Our radars are showing an enormous group of Monolithians coming to reinforce the lost position. Brace yourself!</text>
    </string>
	<string id="no_step_back_defended_position_message">
        <text>Great job, partner. Radars show no further hostile activity in the region. Now come - we have to talk.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="no_step_back_run_fail_message">
        <text>You've just lost your contract mate. Should have hired real fighters...</text>
    </string>
	<string id="no_step_back_details">
        <text>Defend position</text>
    </string>

	<string id="simulation_task_gambling_with_life_name">
		<text>Gambling with life</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_gambling_with_life_text">
		<text>I've accepted a bet with a Freedomer that I'll kill a healthy bloodsucker using only a knife. Hippies on high have weird ideas, but money is money, so...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_gambling_with_life_about">
		<text>Yesterday I've had a trip of my life with one of my dudes. I'm not sure where he took that shit from, but man... it was kicking as hell...\n\nAnyway - back on track. You see - we both like gambling and he came up with a fucked up dare. He said he'd bet a nice sum on anyone killing a bloodsucker using only a knife. One of our fellas - still high as fuck - overheard his talking and went out of the base that night. He never came back, but the bet still stands. Poor guy... wondering what happened to him...\n\nNow where was I? Ah, right - the bet! You seem like a tough guy. Wouldn't you like to try your luck? I'll mount a small camera on your suit so that I can later show that video to my pal. What - you didn't think that I'd tell you his name here, right? Want something for myself out of this as well.\n\nRemember - there's one catch - the mutant has to be healthy. My pal will be able to see any prior wounds on the video and there won't be a payout.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_gambling_with_life_finish">
		<text>You've really impressed me, man! Now let me take this recording to my friend. Here's your share.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gambling_with_life_details">
        <text>Fulfill the bet</text>
    </string>
</string_table>
